All right, so our job was to figure out which of these four options
我们的任务是判断出这四个选项中
would lead to an array that looks like this diagram.
哪个可以创建一个像这个图表中展示的数组
At a quick glance, the variable name is soccer team and
快速扫了一眼 发现变量名称是 soccerTeam and
it has 11 elements in it.
其中有 11 个元素
There are elements at various indices.
各个索引处都有元素
So it's helpful to write down the next number.
最好写下索引号
So it's just easy to remember.
这样更容易记住
Now note that we start at index 0 and go up to index 10.
注意 我们从索引 0 开始 一直到索引 10
This means that the integer 5 is at index 0, integer 10 is at index 1.
意味着索引 0 处是整数 5 索引 1 处是整数 10
The value 23 is at index 4 and the value 1 is at index 10.
值 23 位于索引 4 处 值 1 位于索引 10 处
Now let's review the code options.
我们再来看看代码选项
So this first option creates an integer of a ray length 11, and
第一个选项创建了一个整型数组 长度为 11
has a variable name soccer team.
变量名称是 soccerTeam
So so far it's looking correct.
到目前为止看起来都是正确的
Then we initialize the value 5 at index o1.
然后我们在索引 0 处初始化为值 5
But wait a minute we just said that the value 5 should be at index 0.
等等 我们刚刚提到值 5 应该位于索引 0 处
So this lines incorrect.
所以这行是错误的
And then the next line we're assigning the value 10.
下一行 我们将值 10
At the index 2.
分配到了索引 2 处
But back to the diagram.
再回来看看该图表
We saw that it should be stored at index 1.
我们发现它应该存储在索引 1 处
This code demonstrates a common mistake for beginners.
这段代码演示了初学者会犯的常见错误
When first working with arrays, it's easy to think that the indices go from 1
刚开始使用数组时 很容易就认为索引是从 1 开始的
until the length of the array, which is 11 in this case.
结束处是数组长度 在此示例中即 11
However, in reality we see that it goes from index 0 to index 10 for
但是实际上 对于长度为 11 的数组来说
an array of length 11.
索引是从 0 一直到 10
All right so this means that option 1 is incorrect.
这意味着选项 1 不正确
So let's move to option 2.
我们再看看选项 2
We start off by creating an integer array of length 11.
我们一开始创建了一个长度为 11 的整型数组
This is correct so far but the variable name is just team and
到目前为止正确 但是变量名称仅仅是 team
we wanted it to be called soccer team.
我们希望变量名称是 soccerTeam
So this option is already wrong.
所以这个选项已经不正确了
The rest of the code is also incorrect.
后面的代码也是不正确的
Because we're just retrieving the value of the array of these indices
因为我们只是检索这些索引处的值
instead of assigning values to the spots.
而不是向这些位置分配值
So option two is also incorrect.
所以选项 2 也是不正确的
Now let's take a look at option three.
现在来看看选项 3
We're creating an integer array of length 11 and
我们创建了一个长度为 11 的整型数组
the variable's called soccer team so it's look good so far.
变量的名称叫做 soccerTeam 所以到目前为止看起来正确
We initialize a 0 index to be the value 5 the tenth index
我们将索引 0 初始化为值 5
to be value 4, the tenth index to be the value 1.
第 10 个索引赋为值 4 错了 是值 1
The fourth index to be the value 23.
第 4 个索引赋为值 23
And the first index to be the value 10.
第 1 个索引赋为值 10
Hey, and that's exactly what we want.
嘿 这正是我们需要的
So it matches diagram in the quiz image.
与测试题图片中的图表相符
You may have been concerned that the code assigns values in a random order.
你可能有疑问 代码是按照随机顺序赋的值
So we assign the value of the first element and then the last element and
我们分配了第一个元素的值 然后是最后一个元素的值
then some of the middle ones But it doesn't matter what the order of
然后是一些中间元素 这些语句的顺序是怎样的并没有关系
the statements are because the lines of code are independent from each other.
因为这些代码行相互之间是独立的
At the end of the code snippet, if you want to assign to zeroth index again,
在代码段结束时 如果你想再次为第 0 个索引赋值
you're free to do so.
完全可以的
And the array will just update based on the most recent update to that position.
数组将根据对该位置的最新更新做出更新
Great, so Option 3 is the correct answer.
太棒了 选项 3 是正确答案
And don't worry if you didn't get this correct.
如果你没有答对 也不用担心
This is the first time you're learning about arrays and
这是你第一次学习数组
there'll be a lot more chances coming up for your practice.
以后将有更多的练习机会
In case you were wondering about Option 4, let's still take a look at it.
如果你想看看选项 4 的话 我们一起来研究下
So here in option four we're creating an integer array.
在选项 4 中 我们创建了一个整型数组
But we're capitalizing int since it integer data type is a primitive type,
但是我们将 int 首字母大写了 因为整型数据类型是原始类型
we need to type in iNT with i lowercase.
所以 int 中的 i 应该是小写的
So this is a problem already.
所以这里已经存在问题了
And another problem is that there's a space between the data type and
还有另一个问题是数据类型和数组括号之间
the array brackets.
有个空格
And this will give us an error in Java because it's not a valid array
这样的话 Java 会报错 因为不是有效的数组
declaration.
声明
The subsequent lines of code in option four are also incorrect.
选项 4 后面的代码也不正确
So we're setting string values into these index positions, and
我们向这些索引位置设置了字符串值
you can tell these are strings because they have double quotes.
可以通过双引号判断出这些是字符串
But the problem is that we intended to have an integer array.
但问题是 我们打算创建的是整型数组
So we can't store strings inside of the elements of this array.
所以不能在该数组的元素中存储字符串
And so because of that option four is incorrect.
因此选项 4 不正确